Hello baby! Welcome to a new class.
I'm Emily Rose TV, your English teacher for today.
Last month we learned the alphabet and some numbers.
And today we will learn basic phrases.
Okay.
First, first is, hello, how are you?
Okay?
So, in English, hello, how are you?
Hello, how are you?
Okay, next.
The next phrase is do you like it?
Do you like it?
I also
ok
I finished, yes?
3 sentences is
I want
in English is
Sorry.
In English is I want to.
I want to.
Very transverse.
Do you like it?
The next word is...
I came back.
in English it's turn around
turn around
and for last
it's
que rico
In English is so good.
So good.
Your chicken is so delicious.
I know what to do.
Like the last time.
Turn around.
Do you like it?
But you know, we shouldn't be doing this.
No.
It's bad.
But I like it a lot.
I get a lot of self-esteem in my class.
Yes, you too?
Obviously.
Well, I have like 5 or 6 minutes.
and more students is here.
okay
look
look daddy
oh my god
Oh, yes.
I'm going to sleep now.
I want it.
Si, yo quiero.
Me gusta mucho.
Que rico.
It's so good.
I'm going to go get my hair done.
I'm sorry.
Do you want to sing for your teacher?
I can...
I can help with papers.
I'm going to go and get some papers.
Oh, yes.
Yes, yes, I want to eat, yes, yes.
Yes, I like it a lot, baby.
Yes.
I'm going to go to the bathroom.
Go to the bathroom, baby.
Yes.
Oh my God, how delicious, my love.
Okay.
I need to go.
You need to go. Ready?
I have almost in two minutes.
Bye.